[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "Question": "How many pairs of ribs would the normal human have?",
    "Answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "Question": "Who wrote the classic novel 'Les Miserables'?",
    "Answer": "Victor Hugo"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "Question": "What was the name of Sherlock Holmes Housekeeper?",
    "Answer": "Mrs Hudson"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "Question": "Which actress played the part of Sybil Fawlty in Television's Fawlty Towers?",
    "Answer": "Prunella Scale"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "Question": "What was the title of Beethoven's only opera?",
    "Answer": "Fidelio"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "Question": "Which river flows through the city of Dublin?",
    "Answer": "Liffey"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "Question": "Who appeared with David McCallum in the title role of the TV series 'Sapphire and Steel'?",
    "Answer": "Joanna Lumley"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "Question": "Which Irishman won the Tour de France in 1987?",
    "Answer": "Stephen Roche"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "Question": "In which European country is Cro-Magnon, famous for the discovery of four Palaeolithic skeletons in 1868?",
    "Answer": "France"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "Question": "Which town is the administrative centre for the Open University?",
    "Answer": "Milton Keynes"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "Question": "Who was dedicated to killing Moby Dick?",
    "Answer": "Captain Ahab"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "Question": "In which city is the Sacre Coeur?",
    "Answer": "Paris"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "Question": "What does an entomologist study?",
    "Answer": "Insects"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "Question": "From which course did yesterdays Belgian Grand Prix come?",
    "Answer": "Spa"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "Question": "Who painted The last Supper?",
    "Answer": "Leonardo da Vinci"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "Question": "Which film was the first to feature a laser gun?",
    "Answer": "Goldfinger"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "Question": "What was George Washington's wife's first name?",
    "Answer": "Martha"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "Question": "What is Xenophobia?",
    "Answer": "Hatred Of Foreigners"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "Question": "Which Gilbert And Sullivan Opera is set in Japan?",
    "Answer": "The Mikado"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "Question": "How was Achilles killed?",
    "Answer": "By an arrow in his heel"
  },
  {
"id":"21",
"Question":"Who was the legendary Benedictine monk who invented champagne?",
"answer":"Dom Perignon"
},
{
"id":"22",
"Question":"Name the largest freshwater lake in the world?",
"answer":"Lake Superior"
},{
"id":"23",
"Question":"Where would you find the Sea of Tranquility?",
"answer":"The Moon"
},
{
"id":"24",
"Question":"What is someone who shoes horses called?",
"answer":"A farrier"
},
{
"id":"25",
"Question":"What item of clothing was named after its Scottish inventor?",
"answer":"A Mackintosh"
},
{
"id":"26",
"Question":"What kind of weapon is a falchion?",
"answer":"A sword"
},
{
"id":"27",
"Question":"Which word goes before vest, beans and quartet?",
"answer":"String"
},
{
"id":"28",
"Question":"What is another word for lexicon?",
"answer":"Dictionary"
},
{
"id":"29",
"Question":"Name the seventh planet from the sun.",
"answer":"Uranus"
},
{
"id":"30",
"Question":"Who invented the rabies vaccination?",
"answer":"Louis Pasteur"
},
{
"id":"31",
"Question":"Which is the only American state to begin with the letter 'p'?",
"answer":"Pennsylvania"
},
{
"id":"32",
"Question":"Name the world's biggest island.", 
"answer":"Greenland"
},
{
"id":"33",
"Question":"What is the world's longest river?",
"answer":"Amazon"
},
{
"id":"34",
"Question":"Name the world's largest ocean.",
"answer":"Pacific"
},
{
"id":"35",
"Question":"What is the diameter of Earth?",
"answer":"8,000 miles"
},
{
"id":"36",
"Question":"What is the capital city of Spain?",
"answer":"Madrid"
},
{
"id":"37",
"Question":"Which country is Prague in?", 
"answer":"Czech Republic"
},
{
"id":"38",
"Question":"Which English town was a forerunner of the Parks Movement and the first city in Europe to have a street tram system?", 
"answer":"Birkenhead"
},
{
"id":"39",
"Question":"Name the actor who starred in 142 films including The Quiet Man, The Shootist, The Searchers and Stagecoach.", 
"answer":"John Wayne"
},
{
"id":"40",
"Question":"Name the film noir actress who starred in I Married a Witch, The Glass Key, So Proudly We Hail! and Sullivan's Travels.", 
"answer":"Veronica Lake"
},
{
"id":"41",
"Question":"What is the oldest film ever made, and when was it made?", 
"answer":"Roundhay Garden Scene made in 1888"
},
{
"id":"42",
"Question":"Which actress has won the most Oscars?",
"answer":"Katharine Hepburn"
},
{
"id":"43",
"Question":"Which actress said, 'Fasten your seatbelts. It's going to be a bumpy night,' in All About Eve?",
"answer":"Bette Davis"
},
{
"id":"44",
"Question":"Name the director of the Lord of the Rings trilogy.",
"answer":"Peter Jackson"
},
{
"id":"45",
"Question":"Who played Neo in The Matrix?", 
"answer":"Keanu Reeves"
},
{
"id":"46",
"Question":"Name the actress whose career began at the age of 3, and who went on to star in films such as Contact, Maverick and The Silence of the Lambs?", 
"answer":"Jodie Foster"
},
{
"id":"47",
"Question":"Bray Studios, near Windsor in Berkshire, was home to which famous brand of horror films?", 
"answer":"Hammer Horror"
},
{
"id":"48",
"Question":"In which film did Humphrey Bogart say, 'We'll always have Paris?'", 
"answer":"Casablanca"
},
{
"id":"49",
"Question":"By what name is Lancelot Brown more usually known?", 
"answer":"Capability Brown"
},
{
"id":"50",
"Question":"Name the world famous gardens situated ten miles outside of London, close to the River Thames.", 
"answer":"Kew Gardens"
},
{
"id":"51",
"Question":"How many colours are there in a rainbow?", 
"answer":"7"
},
{
"id":"52",
"Question":"Which garden is considered to be among the Seven Wonders of the Ancient World?",
"answer":"The Hanging Gardens of Babylon"
},
{
"id":"53",
"Question":"What colour is a Welsh poppy?",
"answer":"Yellow"
},
{
"id":"54",
"Question":"What colour is a Himalayan poppy?", 
"answer":"Blue"
},
{
"id":"55",
"Question":"Give the alternative name for a Mountain Ash tree.", 
"answer":"Rowan"
},
{
"id":"56",
"Question":"Which kind of bulbs were once exchanged as a form of currency?", 
"answer":"Tulips"
},
{
"id":"57",
"Question":"By which Latin name was Rosa Gallica previously known?", 
"answer":"Rosa Mundi"
},
{
"id":"58",
"Question":"What colour jersey is worn by the winners of each stage of the Tour De France?", 
"answer":"Yellow"
},
{
"id":"59",
"Question":"Name the only heavyweight boxing champion to finish his career of 49 fights without ever having been defeated?",
"answer":"Rocky Marciano"
},
{
"id":"60",
"Question":"Which sport does Constantino Rocca play?",
"answer":"Golf"
},
{
"id":"61",
"Question":"Name the country where you would find the Cresta Run.", 
"answer":"Switzerland"
},
{
"id":"62",
"Question":"How many times was the Men's Tennis Singles at Wimbledon won by Bjorn Borg?",
"answer":"Five"
},
{
"id":"63",
"Question":"In 2011, which country hosted a Formula 1 race for the first time?",
"answer":"India"
},
{
"id":"64",
"Question":"Name the game played on a lawn called a 'crown green'.", 
"answer":"Bowls"
},
{
"id":"65",
"Question":"Which chess piece can only move diagonally?", 
"answer":"A bishop"
},
{
"id":"66",
"Question":"Name the only footballer to have played for Liverpool, Everton, Manchester City and Manchester United?", 
"answer":"Peter Beardsley"
},
{
"id":"67",
"Question":"In football, who was nicknamed 'The Divine Ponytail'?",
"answer":"Roberto Baggio"
},
{
"id":"68",
"Question":"Name the three primary colours.",
"answer":"Red, yellow and blue"
},
{
"id":"69",
"Question":"Name the famous ballet Russian dancer who changed the face of modern ballet.", 
"answer":"Rudolf Nureyev"
},
{
"id":"70",
"Question":"What is the painting 'La Gioconda' more usually known as?",
"answer":"The Mona Lisa"
},
{
"id":"71",
"Question":"What does the term 'piano' mean?", 
"answer":"To be played softly"
},
{
"id":"72",
"Question":"Name the Spanish artist, sculptor and draughtsman famous for co-founding the Cubist movement.", 
"answer":"Pablo Picasso"
},
{
"id":"73",
"Question":"How many valves does a trumpet have?", 
"answer":"Three"
},
{
"id":"74",
"Question":"If you were painting with tempera, what would you be using to bind together colour pigments?", 
"answer":"Egg yolk"
},
{
"id":"75",
"Question":"What is John Leach famous for making?", 
"answer":"Pottery"
},
{
"id":"76",
"Question":"When was William Shakespeare born?", 
"answer":"23rd April 1564"
},
{
"id":"77",
"Question":"On what date did the Battle of Culloden take place?",
"answer":"16th April 1746"
},
{
"id":"78",
"Question":"Who was Henry VIll's first wife?",
"answer":"Catherine of Aragon"
},
{
"id":"79",
"Question":"When did Margaret Thatcher become Prime Minister?", 
"answer":"1979"
},
{
"id":"80",
"Question":"When did the Cold War end?", 
"answer":"1989"
},
{
"id":"81",
"Question":"Who was the architect who designed the Millennium Dome?",
"answer":"Richard Rogers"
},
{
"id":"82",
"Question":"When did the Eurostar train service between Britain and France start running?",
"answer":"14th November 1994"
},
{
"id":"83",
"Question":"When was the euro introduced as legal currency on the world market?", 
"answer":"1st January 1999"
},
{
"id":"84",
"Question":"What is the oldest surviving printed book in the world?", 
"answer":"The Diamond Sutra, dated at 868 AD"
},
{
"id":"85",
"Question":"In publishing, what does POD mean?", 
"answer":"Print on demand"
},
{
"id":"86",
"Question":"Name the author of On Her Majesty's Secret Service, Dr No and Thunderball, among others.", 
"answer":"Ian Fleming"
},
{
"id":"87",
"Question":"Which Shakespeare play features Shylock?", 
"answer":"The Merchant of Venice"
},
{
"id":"88",
"Question":"Who wrote the novel Death in Venice, which was later made into a film of the same name?", 
"answer":"Thomas Mann"
},
{
"id":"89",
"Question":"Who wrote the Vampire Chronicles, which include the novels Armand, Blood and Gold and Interview with the Vampire?",
"answer":"Anne Rice"
},
{
"id":"90",
"Question":"Who wrote the contemporary children's books about mermaids set on the coast of Cornwall?",
"answer":" Helen Dunmore"
},
{
"id":"91",
"Question":"Name the BBC series about a shipping line set in Liverpool during the late 1800s.", 
"answer":"The Onedin Line"
},
{
"id":"92",
"Question":"Which BBC music programme was broadcast weekly between 1964 and 2006?", 
"answer":"Top of the Pops"
},
{
"id":"93",
"Question":"Alastair Burnett, Sandy Gall, Reginald Bosanquet, Alastair Stewart, Carol Barnes and Trevor McDonald were all regular presenters of which TV programme?", 
"answer":"ITV News at Ten"
},
{
"id":"94",
"Question":"If you had Lafite-Rothschild on your dinner table, what would it be?", 
"answer":"Wine"
},
{
"id":"95",
"Question":"What is sushi traditionally wrapped in?", 
"answer":"Edible seaweed"
},
{
"id":"96",
"Question":"May Queen, Wisley Crab, Foxwhelps and Lane's Prince Albert are all species of what?", 
"answer":"Apples"
},
{
"id":"97",
"Question":"What is allspice alternatively known as?", 
"answer":"Pimento"
},
{
"id":"98",
"Question":"What colour is Absynthe?", 
"answer":"Green"
},
{
"id":"99",
"Question":"What flavour is Cointreau?", 
"answer":"Orange"
},
{
"id":"100",
"Question":"If you were to cut a hare into pieces, marinate it in wine and juniper berries then stew this slowly in a sealed container, what would this recipe be called?", 
"answer":"Jugged hare"
}
]